thomasandfriends.com 2014-06-20

# HIT Entertainment - Terms and Conditions

## HIT Entertainment Privacy Policy

### UPDATED SEPTEMBER 7, 2010

Welcome to HIT Entertainment Limited's ("Hit Entertainment") family of websites (each a "Website") and thank you for visiting. We are committed to providing a quality experience and have developed our Websites to provide an informative and entertaining experience for users. This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes HIT Entertainment's online information practices as they relate to information collected through the Websites; it does not apply to information collected offline or from other sources.

### PARENTS

We encourage parents/guardians to become involved in their children's online experience. Please discuss use of the Internet and disclosure of information on our Websites or any website with your children. Additionally, parents please discuss this Privacy Policy with your children so they better understand how to use our Websites and the kinds of information we may ask of them. With the exception of this section and the "CHILDREN'S PRIVACY" section below, this Privacy Policy governs information about visitors aged 13 and older.

### AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS

Scroll to top

By using our Websites, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or any of its terms, you may not use any HIT Entertainment Website. We may from time-to-time revise this Privacy Policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. By using any HIT Entertainment Website, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of any HIT Entertainment Website after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your understanding and acceptance of such changes.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Scroll to top

If you are 13 or over, we may ask for and collect personal information from you at certain points throughout the Website. Depending on the information and services you request, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, mailing address, payment information (if applicable), birth date and other information. In addition to the information you knowingly provide, HIT Entertainment collects the domain names and IP addresses of its visitors, along with usage statistics (e.g., types of web browsers and operating systems used) and browsing history. This data is used to more efficiently operate HIT Entertainment's business, promote our products and services and administer the Website. HIT Entertainment may combine this information with the other information it collects.

### HOW HIT ENTERTAINMENT USES YOUR INFORMATION

Scroll to top

HIT Entertainment may use your information: (i) to personalize and enhance our Websites and your Internet experience; (ii) to process and respond to inquiries; (iii) for the purposes for which you provided the information; (iv) to provide you with additional product and service opportunities; (v) for internal marketing and demographic studies; (vi) to contact you for non-marketing purposes (such as for feedback or customer service); and (vii) to protect our legal rights or to enforce our Terms of Use http://www.hitentertainment.com/corporate/terms.html. In the future, we may sell some or all or our assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be transferred. We will contractually require buyers to honor our privacy policy.

### INFORMATION SHARING WITH THIRD PARTIES

Scroll to top

HIT Entertainment may disclose your personally identifiable and other information to another entity (i) for purposes of outsourcing one or more of the functions described in the previous section; (ii) to confirm or update information provided by you; (iii) to inform you of important information; (iv) as a part of a sale of assets as described in the previous section. We may also share your information in response to a subpoena, legal order or official request, when we believe you have acted in violation of the Terms of Use <http://www.hitentertainment.com/corporate/terms.html>, or when we believe that doing so may protect our legal rights, your safety or the safety of others. We may also share information collected through one of our Websites with any other of our Websites and with other HIT Entertainment companies.

HIT Entertainment may, from time to time, share your information with third parties so that they can provide you with additional product or service opportunities. Please email us at [privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com](mailto:privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com) if you prefer not to receive these third-party communications.

### SHARING AND USE OF DE-IDENTIFIED INFORMATION

Scroll to top

Information that is de-identified (stripped of any information that could be used to identify you) may be used by HIT Entertainment for any reason and shared freely with third parties.

### SAFETY AND SECURITY

Scroll to top

HIT Entertainment attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures.

### USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY

Scroll to top

We may also collect information using cookies (including HTML and flash cookies), web beacons or similar technologies. These methods permit us to collect various types of information, including which pages you visit, which of our email messages you read, and other information.

### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS

Scroll to top

We may include on our Websites banner or text advertisements from third parties, or for websites operated by third parties, that are not sponsors of and are not affiliated with our Websites. As such, we are not responsible for the content, polices or practices of the websites operated by these third parties. In?addition, these advertisements and/or links do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by us of the content, policies or practices of these websites. All users should check the relevant website's privacy policy and terms of use in order to understand their policies and practices regarding the collection and use of your personal information. For more information on third party ad servers generally, please see [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

### INTERNATIONAL USER NOTICE

Scroll to top

As HIT Entertainment operates globally, it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally, and in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States or the United Kingdom. By using this site, you agree to have your information used and transferred to the United States as set forth in this policy. 

### UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Scroll to top

To ensure that you have as much control over your personally identifiable and other information as possible, you may update your information by contacting us at [privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com](mailto:privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com) or Online Privacy Administrator, 230 Park Avenue South, Suite 1300, New York, NY 10003. We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided, however, that requests to delete information are subject to HIT Entertainment's internal reporting and retention policies and all applicable legal obligations.

### EXTERNAL LINKS

Scroll to top

The Websites may contain links to third-party websites. HIT Entertainment is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Scroll to top

If you are under 13, please do not provide any personally identifiable information to HIT Entertainment except that you may submit your email address in limited circumstances with the understanding that it will not be retained by HIT Entertainment. If you are under 13 and would like to communicate with us in any other way or post something on the Website, please talk to your parents and have them contact us at [privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com](mailto:privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com).

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Scroll to top

If you are a California resident, you are entitled by law to request an Information Sharing Disclosure. If you request it, we will provide you with a notice of your right to prevent sharing of your personal information as well as a cost-free means of doing so. To receive such a notice, submit a request to the email address listed in the section below, specifying that you seek your "California Customer Choice Notice." Please allow thirty days for a response.

### COMMENTS, QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

Scroll to top

If you would like to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, please use the Contact Us form on a Website and enter your comments in the text box, or write us at:

HIT Entertainment  
Attn: Online Privacy Administrator  
230 Park Avenue South  
Suite 1300  
New York, NY 10003
